<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Module 3 on AWS Modernization Workshop with Sysdig</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/50_module_3.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Module 3 on AWS Modernization Workshop with Sysdig</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    
	<atom:link href="//localhost:1313/50_module_3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup CloudTrail Runtime Security</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/50_module_3/51_setup_cloudtrail_runtime_security.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/50_module_3/51_setup_cloudtrail_runtime_security.html</guid>
      <description>If you followed this workshop from the beginning then you should have deployed the CloudTrail CloudFormation Template earlier. If you didn&amp;rsquo;t, then go back and complete this step now Setup CloudTrail Runtime Security, however please note that this can take up to ten minutes to complete.
To check it has been deployed successfully, navigate to https://console.aws.amazon.com/cloudformation/ and search for CloudConnector. You should see it&amp;rsquo;s status is CREATE_COMPLETE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Runtime Cloud Security Threats</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/50_module_3/52_detecting_runtime_cloud_security_threats.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/50_module_3/52_detecting_runtime_cloud_security_threats.html</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s look at an example of AWS threat detection in action with CloudTrail and the Sysdig CloudConnector. To do so we&amp;rsquo;ll create an S3 bucket, and make it public
 Log into Cloud9 Workspace Create an S3 bucket. S3 bucketnames are globally unique, so use your initials combined with a timestamp
INITIALS=&amp;lt;your initial&amp;gt; BUCKETNAME=$INITIALS-$(date +%s) aws s3api create-bucket --bucket $BUCKETNAME --acl public-read  Now delete the S3 bucket&amp;rsquo;s encryption. This should be considered a potential security threat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Checking Security Findings in AWS Security Hub</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/50_module_3/53_checking_security_findings_in_the_aws_security_hub.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/50_module_3/53_checking_security_findings_in_the_aws_security_hub.html</guid>
      <description>You can check these events without leaving the AWS console. This is how findings reported by Sysdig CloudConnector look in the AWS Security Hub:
 Browse to Security Hub and click &amp;lsquo;Findings&amp;rsquo; on the left.   Click on &amp;ldquo;Delete bucket encryption&amp;rdquo; to view all the information you need to take immediate action:   And they appear in JSON format in AWS CloudWatch log streams.
Browse to CloudWatch, and click &amp;lsquo;Log groups &amp;gt; cloud-connector &amp;gt; alerts&amp;rsquo;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>